(Sheldon:)Amy, get the Neosporin,
(Sheldon:)somebody just got burned.
(Leonard:)All right, I tried.
"All right,
I tried."
(Sheldon:)That should be the title
of your autobiography.
(Sheldon:)Ooh, a second-degree burn.
(Amy:)I've got the Neosporin.
(Amy:)Who got hurt?
(Sheldon:)It's a good thing you're cute.
(Raj:)So, I was reading how it's
a good idea for new parents
(Raj:)to take an
infant CPR class.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, we've been
meaning to do that.
(Stuart:)Oh, I know a CPR instructor
who'll come to the house.
- That'd be great.
- I'll give him a call.
(Stuart:)We met when I was sleeping
on the beach
(Stuart:)and he thought I was dead.
(Bernadette:)Thank you again
for cooking.
(Bernadette:)It's getting tough for me
to be on my feet all day.
You just kick back and relax;
I've got it all under control.
(Raj:)Although it was
already under control.